chitkara.edu.in 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy - Chitkara University

## Privacy Policy

You may visit our website without revealing any personal information wherever permissible. Certain transactions may require submission of personal information like profile updates and certain databases. Chitkara University respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that access the information and use the services provided through them. Individually identifiable information about the User is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving the User’s permission, as covered in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy describes Chitkara University’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Chitkara University collects when a User is on the Chitkara University’s website. Chitkara University does not collect any unique information about the User (such as User’s name, email address, age, gender etc.) except when the User specifically and knowingly provides such information on the Website. We will not sell, swap or rent, or otherwise disclose to any third party any personal information for commercial purpose and such information will be utilized only for the purpose stated. To accomplish such purpose we may disclose the information to our employees, consultants and other concerned having a genuine need to know the information.

Our web server may record the numerical Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, Information about your browser and operating system, date and time of access and page which linked you to our website. This information may be used to administer and improve our website and to generate aggregate statistical reports and such like purposes. We may use cookies and pixels or transparent GIF files to track session information and/or to deliver customizable and personalized services and information and/or for other purposes of website such information is anonymous and not personally identifiable.

Please be aware, however, that Chitkara University will release specific personal information about the User if required to do so in the following circumstances: 

a) in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, statute, or court order, or 

b) if any of User’s actions on Chitkara University’s website violate the Terms of Service or any of Chitkara University’s guidelines for specific services, or

c) to protect or defend Chitkara University’s legal rights or property, the Chitkara University site, or Chitkara University Users; or

d) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the security, integrity of Chitkara University website/offerings.

##### Links to Other Web Sites

The Site contains links to other Web sites that are not controlled by us and are not covered by this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, security or content of such websites. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions express in such Web sites, and such Web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked for accuracy or completeness by us. Inclusion of any linked Web site on our Site does not imply approval or endorsement of the linked Web site by us. If you decide to leave our Site and access these third-party sites, you do so at your own risk.

##### Information and Press Releases

The Site may contain information and press releases about us. While this information was believed to be accurate as of the date prepared, we disclaim any duty or obligation to update this information or any press releases. Information about companies other than ours contained in the press release or otherwise, should not be relied upon as being provided or endorsed by us.

While we make our best efforts to protect the privacy of users however we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

This privacy policy may be revised/modified/amended at any point of time at the sole discretion of the University.
